{
    "subject": "resource/Fernando_Pessoa",
    "predicate": "ontology/influenced",
    "object": "resource/Miguel_Torga",
    "human_readable": "Fernando Pessoa was influenced by Miguel Torga.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9553952217102051,
            "question": "How did Fernando Pessoa's literary style reflect the influence of Miguel Torga?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9533988833427429,
            "question": "What impact did Miguel Torga have on Fernando Pessoa's work?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9318488836288452,
            "question": "Who was Fernando Pessoa influenced by?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9138981699943542,
            "question": "What were some common themes explored by both Fernando Pessoa and Miguel Torga?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.895330548286438,
            "question": "Were there other writers besides Miguel Torga who influenced Fernando Pessoa?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7995968461036682,
            "question": "Can you provide examples of how Miguel Torga's work is reflected in Fernando Pessoa's writing?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7960258722305298,
            "question": "What is the relationship between Fernando Pessoa and Miguel Torga?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7750847935676575,
            "question": "Name a writer who influenced Fernando Pessoa."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6591261029243469,
            "question": "Can you tell me about the literary influences on Fernando Pessoa?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6421682834625244,
            "question": "Who was Miguel Torga?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Fernando Pessoa was influenced by Miguel Torga.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8489_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me about the literary influences on Fernando Pessoa?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8489_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Name a writer who influenced Fernando Pessoa.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8489_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the relationship between Fernando Pessoa and Miguel Torga?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8489_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8489_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8489_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8489_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8489_48.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8489_52.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8489_59.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8489_71.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8489_74.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8489_79.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8489_81.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'no'} \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in JSON format:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nThe reason for this answer is that the documents do not mention an influence of Miguel Torga on Fernando Pessoa. While both writers are Portuguese, and there are mentions of their works and lives, there is no indication of a direct influence from one to another."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The provided documents do not mention any influence of Miguel Torga on Fernando Pessoa. While information about Miguel Torga is present, there is no indication that he influenced Fernando Pessoa in the context given."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"no\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "mistral": {
            "reason": "There is no evidence or information in the context that suggests Fernando Pessoa was influenced by Miguel Torga. On the contrary, the context states that Torga himself was inspired by other authors like Pessoa.",
            "category": -1
        },
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "The provided text states that Miguel Torga was inspired by Fernando Pessoa, not the other way around.",
            "category": -1
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "There is no information provided to suggest a connection between Fernando Pessoa and Miguel Torga, let alone an influence of one on the other. The context only mentions that both are Portuguese writers, but it does not imply any relationship or interaction between them.",
            "category": -1
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "reason": "The context information does not provide any evidence suggesting that Fernando Pessoa was influenced by Miguel Torga. Instead, the text highlights Pessoa's significant influence on other authors and artists, such as Jos\u00e9 Saramago and Michael Barrett, and discusses his concept of heteronyms and esoteric influences.",
            "category": -1
        }
    }
}